launching with the safe default policy: build\examples\remote-support-showcase\hyremote-remote-support-showcase.exe --port 5967 --auto-start --test-seconds 240
remote access started by the application itself: True
application window hwnd=64424488; local input method: physical key events
step A - the starting policy is view-only
  view-only: opening a fresh viewer
  view-only: application reported a connected client = True
  view-only: remote 'a' reached the application = False
step B - local enablement of control (the payload restarts remote access on a policy change)
    local probe: REMOTE_INPUT enabled observed on attempt 2 (space)
  REMOTE_INPUT enabled observed: True; remote access restarted by the payload: True
  control mode: opening a fresh viewer
  control mode: application reported a connected client = True
  control mode: remote 'a' reached the application = False
step C - policy back to view-only on the live session
  REMOTE_INPUT disabled observed: False; remote access restarted again: False
application control lines: ['REMOTE_STARTED 5967', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 0', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 1', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 0', 'REMOTE_INPUT enabled', 'REMOTE_STARTED 5967', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 0', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 1', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 0']
application still running: True
=== boundary status ===
  A view-only blocked remote input: True
  B control mode delivered remote input: False
  C returning to view-only blocked remote input again: not reached
  held-state balance across the transition: NOT instrumented (no key probe on this payload); the claim stays with the basic examples' held-holder path
second attempt finished
