launching: build\examples\remote-support-showcase\hyremote-remote-support-showcase.exe --port 5962 --remote-input --auto-start --test-seconds 150
control mode requested at startup (--remote-input) and remote access auto-started
REMOTE_STARTED observed: True
  window hwnd=27924414 796x619 class='Qt683QWindowIcon' title='HyRemote Remote Support Showcase'
selected application window hwnd=27924414
viewer attached: SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 1 observed: True
capture before stop: showcase-before-stop.png 36081 B
(this capture is the proof that the viewer was being served while remote input is on)
holding a modifier remotely and NOT releasing it, then stopping locally
Shift is held by the viewer; the holder will never send the release
foreground taken for the local stop: True
attempt 1: local space sent (physical)
explicit stop observed while control mode was active: True
application control lines: ['SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 1', 'SHOWCASE_KEY key=16777248', 'SHOWCASE_KEY key=16777248', 'SHOWCASE_KEY key=16777248', 'SHOWCASE_KEY key=32', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 0', 'SHOWCASE_CLIENTS 0', 'REMOTE_STOPPED']
application still running after the stop: True
application window still present: True
new viewer attempt after the stop failed as expected: ConnectionRefusedError - the listener really is closed
restarting locally to prove the application is still functional, not merely alive
application restarted remote access after the stop (still functional): True
=== E1 step 6 status ===
  control mode active before the stop: True (--remote-input, remote start)
  modifier held by the viewer at the moment of the stop: True (never released)
  explicit stop while controlled: True
  application alive after the stop: True
  listener closed: True (fresh connection attempt failed)
  application still functional (restart observed): True
  held-state balance: NOT instrumented on this payload - the showcase has no key probe and the product side ruled out adding one to the frozen candidate; that claim stays with the basic examples' held-holder path
showcase terminated
