launching: build\examples\qpa-proxy-existing-app\hyremote-qpa-proxy-existing-app.exe -platform hyremote:hyremote-port=5964:hyremote-input=true --test-seconds 150
proxy active + serving observed: True
proxy's own lines: ['HyRemote QPA Proxy active; native delegate: "windows" remote address: "127.0.0.1" port: 5964 remote input: true', 'HyRemote QPA application remote access active on "127.0.0.1" 5964 remote input: true']
  window hwnd=532992 876x599 title='Existing Qt Operations Console'
top-level window count BEFORE: 1
capture main window: 16800 B
opening the application's diagnostics dialog from the REMOTE side via its File menu
menu popup frame: 3586 changed pixels, bbox (5, 0, 207, 558)
top-level window count with the menu open: 2
top-level window count with the dialog open: 2
  window hwnd=1909198 436x279 title='Independent diagnostics window'
  window hwnd=532992 876x599 title='Existing Qt Operations Console'
dialog appeared (count grew): True
composed view changed vs the main-window frame: 72179 changed pixels, bbox (6, 10, 845, 558)
delivering remote text now - the dialog's own field holds it
frame after remote text into the dialog: 108 changed pixels, bbox (359, 222, 375, 237)
closing that surface LOCALLY while it holds the delivered input
posting Escape to the dialog's own window hwnd=1909198 title='Independent diagnostics window' (no foreground needed, so no other application can receive this key)
top-level window count after the local close: 1
dialog gone (count back to the baseline): True
composed view after the close vs the main-window frame: 765 changed pixels, bbox (6, 545, 152, 558)
the proxy must still serve and still accept remote input, application alive
remote input after the close still changes the view: 52 changed pixels, bbox (206, 66, 214, 81)
proxy's own lines at the end: ['HyRemote QPA Proxy active; native delegate: "windows" remote address: "127.0.0.1" port: 5964 remote input: true', 'HyRemote QPA application remote access active on "127.0.0.1" 5964 remote input: true']
application still running: True
visible top-level windows at the end: 1
=== accepted weakness of this instrument ===
  frames and window counts show the surface appearing, holding remote input, disappearing on a
  local close, and the proxy continuing to serve; they CANNOT show whether the application
  retained a synthetic press that the hidden surface had received.
E4 child-surface run finished
